字幕由：制作 （娱乐版）
欢迎加入我们：QQ 20957070  E-mail: richard2008jz@hotmail.com
这就是我,彼得・帕克。
It's me, Peter Parker.
你们友好的邻居... 你知道。
Your friendly neighborhood... you know.
我自从童年时被一只蜘蛛咬了以后发生很多事情。。
I've come a long way from being the boy who was bit by a spider.
回顾过去，对于我来说没有什么走向正确的。。
Back then, nothing seemed to go right for me.
现在的 ... - 呜呜声,看,它是蜘蛛-人!
Now... - Wow, look, it's Spider-Man!
人们是真的喜欢我.
people really like me.
嗨,在附近黏住! 它将要再一次分开需要很久。 - 是的... - 那最好。
Hey, stick around! It's gonna start again in a couple minutes. - Yeah... - That's OK.
城市是安全的和健全的。
The city is safe and sound.
猜测我有与……有关那.
Guess I've had something to do with that.
我的叔父 本 会很骄傲的 .
My uncle Ben would be proud.
(为什么纽约人爱蜘蛛侠?)
我仍然去上学的 , 是我们班的尖子生.
I still go to school, top of my class.
现在，汉密尔顿函数向我们说明
Now, the Hamiltonian shows us
能量级位被电场扰乱。
that the energy levels are perturbed by the electric field.
从这个母体的形式,
From the form of this matrix,
我们能看见。。?。
we can see...?
沃特森 小姐? - 只有 m=0 分配量会被影响。
Miss Stacey? - That only the m=0 quantum states are affected.
正确的! 很努力,沃特森 小姐。
Correct! Good work, Miss Stacey.
帕克。
Parker.
你是否得到了某些物质的增加?
You got something to add?
不,先生。
No, sir.
和我在爱方面
And I'm in love
由于我的心中的少女 .
with the girl of my dreams.
嗨。 Um,沃特森 小姐为我留下了一张票?
Hi. Um, Miss Watson left a ticket for me?
彼得・帕克。
Peter Parker.
对不起。 借过。 谢谢。
Excuse me. Sorry. Thank you.
她是我的女朋友!
It's my girlfriend!
哈利!
Harry!
我需要和你说话。
I need to talk to you.
解释一下。
Explain things.
对 我的父亲告诉我。
Tell it to my father.
他从小养育的人。
Raise him from the dead.
我是你的朋友,哈利。
I'm your friend, Harry.
我关心 你的父亲。
I cared about your father.
玛丽。
MJ.
彼得。
Peter.
我是行吗？ - 行?
Was I good? - Good?
你很很棒。 你是。。。 - 你说很棒的?
You were great. You were... - You say great?
我爱我的花。 它们很美丽。
I love my flowers. They're beautiful.
而且那些是哈利送来的。
And those are from Harry.
他今晚在这里吗? - 是的,我外面偶遇他。
Was he here tonight? - Yeah, I ran into him outside.
无论如何和你在一起家伙是作什麽的?
What's with you guys anyway?
它是复杂的。
It's complicated.
再一次告诉我,我真的是行吗?
Tell me again, was I really good?
我是如此神经紧张。 我的膝正在摇动。
I was so nervous. My knees were shaking.
你的膝很好。 - 鼓掌不很大声。
Your knees were fine. - The applause was not very loud.
是的, 它是……
Yes, it was.
它是音响学。 所有的声音主要是关注散布的频率。
It's the acoustics. It's all about diffusion.
它保存来自配列的音波。
It keeps the sound waves from grouping.
你看见, 当音波, 他们繁殖, 然后它是像一... - 你是如此的一个书呆子。
You see, when the sound waves, they propagate, then it's like an... - You are such a nerd.
你看见那一个吗?
Did you see that one?
你知道什么?
You know what?
我想要为我的歌迷在台上唱
I'd like to sing on stage for the rest of my life
所以你在第一排中。
with you in the first row.
我将在那里。
I'll be there.
告诉我你爱我。
Tell me you love me.
我爱你。
I love you.
我爱你很多。
I love you so much.
但我总是有。
I always have.
你在这里不能藏,打火石。
You can't hide here, Flint.
我就在这里看见我的女儿。
I'm just here to see my daughter.
你是一个被逃脱的囚犯。
You are an escaped convict.
警官正在找寻你。
The cops are looking for you.
你不在靠近她有。
You're not getting near her.
你只是一个通常的小偷。
You're nothing but a common thief.
也许平凡的你杀了一个人。
You maybe even killed a man.
它并不是那样。
It wasn't even like that.
不是。
Wasn't.
我为我所正在做的有了好的理由。
I had good reason for what I was doing.
而且是事实。
And that's the truth.
你和事实，在监狱中坐下,每天一日三餐。
You and the truth, sitting in prison, having three meals a day together.
我住在一所监狱。 它是一个很棒的事实。
I live in a prison. It's a great truth.
而且是你遗留 的事实。
And that is the truth that you left behind.
在卧室中的就在那里。
Right there in that bedrooom.
我想念你。
I missed you.
我也想念你,爸爸。
I missed you too, Daddy.
我发誓
I promise
我再一次将使你健康。
I'll make you healthy again.
无论它拿什麽。
Whatever it takes.
我将拿钱。 - 你滚出这里。
I'll get the money. - You get out of here.
现在。
Now.
我不是一个坏的人。
I'm not a bad person.
只是一时有了坏的运气。
Just had bad luck.
彼得,她是什么?
Peter, what is it?
她是 玛丽 。。。
It's MJ...
我将要 要求她与我结婚!
I'm gonna ask her to marry me!
哦,彼得! 哦!
Oh, Peter! Oh!
你叔父 班 要求了我与他结婚的天,
The day that uncle Ben asked me to marry him,
我如此被惊吓而且刺激的。
he was so scared and excited.
而且非常年轻的。
And very young.
而且我如此猛烈爱他。
And I loved him so fiercely.
然后你是的说,权利?
Then you said yes, right?
我想要是的说号码, 但是我说号码
No. I wanted to say yes, but I said no.
我不准备好,
I wasn't ready,
他也不是。
neither was he.
因此我们从容不迫。
So we took our time.
盼望它。
Looked forward to it.
不  想要什麽也没用～我遇事物信赖 但是爱。
Didn't want to run into something with nothing to count on but love.
一个男人必须了解
A man has to be understanding
而且在他自己之前放了他的妻子。
and put his wife before himself.
你能做那吗? 彼得
Can you do that, Peter?
是的。 我认为我能。
Yeah. I think I can.
然后你有我的祝福。
Then you have my blessing.
我希望你有考虑一份适当的提议。
I hope you've considered a proper proposal.
你的叔父有了它全部被计划。
Your uncle had it all planned.
他星期日将我带到海滩。
He took me to the beach one Sunday.
而且他在送我一件精彩漂亮的泳衣中。
He was a knockout in his bathing suit.
而且我,我不算看起来太坏 我自己。
And I, I didn't look too bad myself.
我们是非常好的游泳者。
We were very good swimmers.
它是一个美丽的日子,
It was a beautiful day,
而且他说: "让我们游泳到那岛"。
and he said: "Let's swim to the island."
而且在那岛,
And at the island,
我们发现了一棵旧的树和一个完美的地点,
we found a perfect spot by an old tree,
而且我们向着天空躺下而且看向上。
and we lay down and looked up at the sky.
然後他说,"闭上你的眼睛五秒"
And then he said, "Close your eyes, May."
而且我做。 然後他说," 开着的它们."
And I did. And then he said, "Open them."
而且我做了。
And I did.
他正在握住这个戒指。
And he was holding this ring.
眼花撩乱的我,当时……
Dazzling, in front of me.
我想它是太阳。
I thought it was the sun.
我们将会在结婚的 50 年
We'd be married 50 years
未来的八月。。。 是否...
come August... if...
如此。
So.
我希望你使它非常特别
I hope you make it very special
因为玛丽珍。
for Mary Jane.
做些事情让她无法忘记。
Do something she'll never forget.
给她这。
Give her this.
快点 。
Come on.
带它。
Take it.
哈利。 - 你知道这是过去,彼得 。
Harry. - You knew this was coming, Pete.
听我的话! 不是我杀你的父亲!
Listen to me! I didn't kill your father!
他正在尝试杀我。 但是他杀了他自己。
He was trying to kill me. He killed himself.
闭嘴!
Shut up!
我是停止的这一切，彼得!
I'm still here, Peter!
我讨厌那些东西。
Hate those things.
哈利。
Harry.
哈利!
Harry!
哦我的上帝。
Oh my God.
哈利!
Harry!
快点 !
Come on!
上帝!
God!
200. - 而且清楚的!
200. - And clear!
没有回应。 - 再休整。 让我们再来一次。
No response. - Recharge. Let's go again.
清楚的!
Clear!
没有回应。
No response.
我们再电一次。 而且清楚的!
We charge it one more time. And clear!
警长 Stacey。
Captain Stacey.
这是什么? - 打火石 Marko, 家伙是到我们狱里杀人。
What's this? - Flint Marko, the guy we tied to the Ben Paker homicide.
什么有关他? - 他仅仅 Rikers 爆发。
What about him? - He just broke out of Rikers.
而且? - 他是在跑路中。
And? - He's on the run.
他是在 marshlands 中。 我认为我们得找到了他。
He's in the marshlands. I think we got him.
他在那里!
There he is!
"危险 粒子物理学测试设备 保存出"
"DANGER PARTICLE PHYSICS TEST FACILITY KEEP OUT"
印托,去西方边。 托马麦,去东边。
*Euton*, take the west side. *Tommy*, take the east.
他去哪里了?
Where'd he go?
那是它。 它被收费。 - 权利。
That's it. It's charged. - Right.
达利丽, 我们得到了一个小变动在 1之上.
Donnie, we got a little fluctuation on 1.
有在某方面的改变矽块。
There's a change in the silicon mass.
它可能是一只鸟。 当我们向上点燃它的时候 , 它将会飞离开。
It's probably a bird. It'll fly away when we fire it up.
开始 demoleculisation 。
Initiating demoleculisation.
他好吗? - 他正在恢复。
How is he? - He's gonna be OK.
但是在脑部有一些记忆损害。
But there's been some memory impairment.
特别地他的短期记忆。
Particularly his short-term memory.
现在，他不能记得意外事件
Right now, he can't remember the accident
或最近发生在他身上的任何事。
or anything that happened to him recently.
它是长期的吗?
Is it permanent?
它可以是。
It could be.
只有时间将会看得出。
Only time will tell.
是否你想要看见他，他是醒的。
He's awake if you want to see him.
Uh-- 也许我应该等候。
Uh-- maybe I should wait.
Nah,他很好。 最好安静些， 让他休息。
Nah, it's fine. Just keep it brief. Allow him to rest.
嗨，伙伴。 - 嗨。
Hey, buddy. - Hey.
碰撞了我的头。
Hit my head.
是的。
Yeah.
医生说我是在意外事件中。 肇事者肇事后逃离现场。
Doctor said I was in an accident. Hit and run.
我不记得许多的事情。
I don't remember much of anything.
我的父亲--
My father--
他死于权利?
he died, right?
这是所有的如此怪异。
This is all so weird.
嗨。 我已经尽可能很快了。
Hi. I got here as fast as I could.
我知道那个脸。
I know that face.
你好吗？
How are you doing?
我不知道。
I don't know.
我记得的最后事物,我正在落下。。。
Last thing I remember, I was falling...
某处。
somewhere.
你仍然好。
You're still fine.
我们爱你,哈利。
We love you, Harry.
它感觉起来像
It feels like
不知何故我走了非常长的时间之久。
somehow I've been gone for a really long time.
现在我是后面的家。
Now I'm back home.
最好把你带回来的。
It's good to have you back.
对不起, 我正在去必须问你用支索撑住轻快地奔跑,好?
I'm sorry, I'm gonna have to ask you guys to scoot, OK?
好。 - 好, 谢谢你。
OK. - All right, thank you.
好吧，我明天将看见你。
Well, I'll see you tomorrow.
是的,很棒的。
Yeah, great.
我认为他正在好起来。
I think he's gonna be fine.
我也这麽认为。
Think so.
而且你家伙像是很很棒。 - 是的。
And you guys seem great. - Yeah.
你有可爱的朋友。
You have lovely friends.
我最好的朋友。
My best friends.
我将会为他们给我的生活。
I'd give my life for them.
进来? - 是我。 - 哦! 嗨!
Yeah? - It's me. - Oh! Hey!
我认为我不能打开门。
You know I can't open the door.
你再一次被欺骗?
It's stuck again?
过来帮帮我。
Come on and help me.
我正在过来。
I'm coming.
检讨。 - 哦!
The review. - Oh!
那憎恨它。 他们憎恨我。
The hated it. They hated me.
好吧，他们不能憎恨你。
Well, they can't hate you.
"年轻的 沃特森 小姐是一个漂亮的少女。
"The young Miss Watson is a pretty girl.
" 容易的在眼睛上, 但是不在耳朵上。
"Easy on the eyes, but not on the ears.
"她的轻轻越过第一排不携带……"。
"Her small voice didn't carry past the first row."
那是荒谬的。 我是就在那里。
That's ridiculous. I was right there.
你是在第一排中。
You were in the first row.
是的, 但是...
Yeah, but that's...
听。 你很很棒。
Listen. You were great.
那是一位批评家。
That's a critic.
这是某物 你必须习惯它。
This is something you're gonna have to get used to.
相信我,我知道。
Believe me, I know.
蜘蛛-人 拿丝攻击…… - 这不是有关你。
Spider-Man gets attacked all the time. - This isn't about you.
它是有关我。
It's about me.
它是有关我的事业事。 - 我知道，而且我仅仅正在说,
It's about my career. - I know, and I'm just saying,
你不能让它带来你下。
you can't let it bring you down.
你仅仅必须相信 你自己。 和你一起拉你自己,
You just gotta believe in yourself. You pull yourself together,
而且你在马上正确了背面。 - 不  给我马事物。
and you get right back on the horse. - Don't give me the horse thing.
试着去了解我感觉如何。
Try to understand how I feel.
它很正直。。。
It's just...
我看着这些字,
I look at these words,
而且它像我的父亲写信给他们。
and it's like my father wrote them.
所有的汽车。 所有的汽车在邻近第 54 和第 6个大街,请报告。 由控制伸颈。 要小心。
All cars. All cars in the vicinity of 54th and 6th Ave, please report. Crane out of control. Approach with caution.
有情况。
Go get 'em, tiger.
对不起。
Sorry.
哦我的上帝。
Oh my God.
七原子起重机 到中央的。  *****.
Seven *Atom* to central. That crane *****.
它比我们想的要严重。 我们现在需要一个主要的动员。
It's bigger than we thought. We're gonna need a major mobilization right away.
加速器必须插入水中! 现在!
Just gotta *douse the accelerator! Now!
好,格蕾。 我已经得到一个秘密。 它是我的呼叫。
OK, Gwen. I've got a secret. It's my call for ya.
那件事物在我的背景方面做是什么?
What is that thing doing in my background?
警长 Stacey, 这家伙看来由它的注射器. 他们不能停止起重机。
Captain Stacey, the guys look *out of shot of it*. They can't shut down the crane.
打电话叫消防队。
Get Edison on the phone.
让他们封锁整个的区段。
Have them kill the power of the whole block.
你还好吧?
Are you all right?
它正在回来!
It's coming back!
哦我的上帝。 她是 格蕾!
Oh my God. It's Gwen!
什么?
What?
她正在那里上面做什么?
What's she doing up there?
我不知道。 我仅仅昨晚看见了她。 她说她有了一个车模展。
I don't know. I just saw her last night. She said she had a modeling gig.
你是谁? - 我是 布洛克 ，先生。
Who are you? - It's Brock, sir.
埃迪・布洛克JR。
Eddie Brock, jr.
我在“每日广播”工作。
I work at the Daily Bugle.
而且我正在和你的女儿约会。
And I'm dating your daughter.
你好? - 是的。
You OK? - Yeah.
我很好。
I'm fine.
谢谢你。
Thank you.
嗨， 蜘蛛,稍等。 广播 需要一张相片。
Hey, Spidey, hold on. Bugle needs a photo.
谢谢上帝你是好。 - 爸爸!
Thank God you're OK. - Daddy!
嗨。 我是新的家伙。 - 新的家伙?
Hey. I'm the new guy. - New guy?
从现在开始，我正在为你做宣传。
From now on, I'm gonna be taking shots of you for the Bugle.
如此-- 微笑! 你正在微笑吗?
So-- smile! Are you smiling?
另一个家伙在哪里? - 彼得・帕克?
Where's the other guy? - Peter Parker?
是的,um,看,在你和我之间--
Yeah, um, look, between you and me--
这家伙是一业余者的类型。
The guy's kind of an amateur.
注意你,他的东西使你稍微看。。。 着胖了点。
Have you noticed, his stuff makes you look a little... bloated.
仅仅一个小小矮矮胖胖的。 - 好...
Just a little chunky. - OK...
不  你现在不再烦恼,伙伴。
Don't have to worry about that anymore, buddy.
Dazzeling。
Dazzeling.
仅仅稍微某物 在广告部门中的男孩和我想的 。
Just a little something the boys in the ad department and I whipped up.
正如你所知,喇叭的循环 有的是漂亮的好。
As you know, circulation of the Bugle has been pretty good.
虽然不和纽约时报一样
Though not as good as the New York Times
或每日的新闻
or the Daily News
或职位或一些其他的比较小的... - 继续它,低智!
or the Post or several other smaller... - Get on with it, moron!
什么? - 你的血压,Jameson 先生。
What? - Your blood pressure, Mr Jameson.
你的妻子告诉我告诉你看忿怒。 - 你告诉我的妻子。。。
Your wife told me to tell you to watch the anger. - You tell my wife...
谢谢你。
Thank you.
因此,我计划这个活动:
So, I propose this campaign:
" 每日的吹喇叭(召集)"-- 那是明显的。
"DAILY BUGLE" -- that's obvious.
"它是臀部,它是现在"-- 我提出那一个。
"IT'S HIP, IT'S NOW" -- I came up with that one.
"它是呜呜声"-- 那实际上是艾力克的。
"IT'S WOW" -- that's actually Eric's.
"及如何 !" -- 那再一次是我。
"AND HOW!" -- that's me again.
到你吃药的时间。
Time to take your pill.
不是那一个。
Not that one.
喝许多水。
Drink plenty of water.
谢谢你。
Thank you.
继续。
Continue.
他很忙碌。
He's busy.
哦,不,我就在这里和你说话,小孩。 (- 那种味道是什么?)
Oh, no, I'm just here to talk to you, babe. (- What's that smell?)
那是稍微某物叫做
That's a little something called
"容易的美好 'n'".
"Nice 'n' Easy".
什么是在你身上? - 它叫做 " 走开" 。
What's on you? - It's called "Go Away".
那是最哑的主意你曾经已经有。 你有有一些使人畏缩的... - 血压。
That is the dumbest idea you've ever had. You have had some daunting... - Blood pressure.
嗨,你正要去哪里?
Hey, where are you going?
你是谁? - 你上星期雇用了他。
Who are you? - You hired him last week.
自由工作者。 - 我做的? 那种味道是什么?
Freelance. - I did? What's that smell?
Brock,先生。 爱德华 Brock 年少者。
Brock, sir. Edward Brock junior.
呜呜声,我真的喜欢那件衬衫。
Wow, I really like that shirt.
这里。 它是起重机意外事件。 办理退房手续轻的来源。
Here. It's a crane accident. Check out the light source.
他喜欢我的衬衫。
He likes my shirt.
嗨，贝蒂。 - 嗨， 彼得 。 你最好进入那里。
Hey, Betty. - Hey, Pete. You better get in there.
一个新的家伙。 他正在尝试卖一些 蜘蛛 相片。
A new guy. He's trying to sell some Spidey photos.
Uh。 谢谢。
Uh. Thanks.
帕克! 你迟到! 也许太晚。 Bruckner 这里打了对它的 ya 。
Parker! You're late! Maybe too late. Bruckner here beat ya to it.
它是 Brock ，先生。 爱德华 Brock 年少者。 - 我得到你这。
It's Brock, sir. Edward Brock junior. - I got you this.
但是他得到我这的。
But he got me this.
等候。 你拿的什么? 我当时没看见你。 - 那么你拿那个高度?
Wait. How'd you get that? I didn't see you. - How'd you get that high?
攀登。 几乎从一个旗竿跌下来。
Climbed. Nearly fell off a flagpole.
一个旗竿?
A flagpole?
哪一个我们使用吗? - 我喜欢 布洛克的。
Which one do we use? - I like Bernstein's.
它比较好。 - 也比较廉宜的。
It's better. - Cheaper, too.
祝贺,孩子。 我们将会使用你的努力而且支付你 50块钱。
Congratulations, son. We'll use your shot and pay you 50 bucks.
Uh-- 所有的权利,JJ。 我是你的男人。
Uh-- all right, JJ. I'm your man.
我知道更多有关制造一张好的照片东西
I know more about what makes a good picture
比较在这个城镇中的任何摄影师。 看见了,摄影,他是不是差不多
than any photographer in this town. See, photography, it's not just about
-- 没有犯罪 -- 旗竿。 无论什么。
-- no offense -- flagpoles. Whatever.
它有关照明的事情。 作文。 戏剧。
It's about lighting. Composition. Drama.
我需要一种职员工作,先生。
I want a staff job, sir.
我有一个我想要结婚的少女,和--
I have a girl that I intend to marry, and--
我有这个愚蠢的一点点梦-- 有我们的时间最好的报纸编者之一的工作。
I have this stupid little dream of-- working with one of the greatest newspaper editors of our time.
J. 约拿 Jameson。
J. Jonah Jameson.
好吧，我们确实有一打开。
Well, we do have an opening.
摆脱的詹森,记得? - 你开除了他。 - 无论什么。
Johnson quit, remember? - You fired him. - Whatever.
等候分钟。 我知道制造一张好的照片东西  ,
Wait a minute. I know what makes a good picture,
而且我有是这里有很长的一段时间。 如果有一种职员工作,
and I've been here for a long time. If there's a staff job,
Jameson 先生,我认为我该得到它。
Mr Jameson, I think I deserve it.
他是正确的,约拿。 彼得是和我们在一起达数年之久。
He's right, Jonah. Peter's been with us for years.
他被做一种很棒的工作。
He's done a great job.
你想要一种职员工作, 和你需要一种职员工作。
You want a staff job, and you want a staff job.
任何人都关心 我所要的?
Anybody care about what I want?
我做。 - 闭嘴。 滚出去。
I do. - Shut up. Get out.
我真的为二毛五分的罪犯能看见蜘蛛-人 他需要的是民众。
I want the public to see Spider-Man for the two-bit criminal he really is.
他是假货。 他充满 stickum 。
He's a fake. He's full of stickum.
在行动中捕捉他。
Catch him in the act.
"有饼干汽水瓶的他 蜘蛛-人".
"Spider-Man with his hand in the cookie jar".
任何人带来我要的相片 就找到工作。
Whoever brings me that photo gets the job.
你是作什麽的候补因为, 春节? 去,去,去!
What are you waiting for, Chinese New Year? Go, go, go!
我是在他上,老板。
I'm on it, boss.
你将会无法拿那射击。
You'll never get that shot.
我们将会看见。
We'll see.
你知道,
You know,
我猜测一个人能有差别。
I guess one person can make a difference.
'Nuff 说。
'Nuff said.
欢迎来家,哈利。
Welcome home, Harry.
谢谢你是没关系 的上帝。
Thank God you're all right.
谢谢,伯拿。
Thanks, Bernard.
开胃酒? - 确信。
Aperitif? - Sure.
给你一个小归国礼物。
Got you a little homecoming present.
Wha-- 它是你的旧球! - 是的。
Wha-- It's your old ball! - Yeah.
谢谢,伙伴。
Thanks, buddy.
我们在后院中是漂亮的前锋, 我们不是?
We were pretty good in the backyard, weren't we?
我们是可怕的。 而且我们为 varsity 队试出。
We were terrible. And we tried out for the varsity team.
是的,为拉拉队长。 - 玛丽。
Yeah, for the cheerleaders. - Right.
嗨,我有任何的女朋友吗?
Hey, do I have any girlfriends?
我不  知道。 - 你不?
I don't know. - You don't?
嗨 伯拿,我有任何的女朋友吗? - 不我知道 ,先生。
Hey Bernard, do I have any girlfriends? - Not that I know of, sir.
那是相当凉爽的途径,哼!?
That's a pretty cool pass, huh?
它是好。
It's OK.
好像我不在为钱烦恼。
Looks like I'm not worrying for money.
号码
No.
好吧，我打赌我能将这件小女朋友事物转回头。
Well, I bet I can turn this little girlfriend thing around.
你知道,
You know,
他总是感激了你如何帮助了我经过中学。
he always appreciated how you helped me through high school.
我仅仅愿我可以记得更多有关他。
I just wish I could remember more about him.
他爱你。
He loved you.
那才是主要。
That's the main thing.
嗨,让我们在厨房中看看。
Hey, let's watch the game in the kitchen.
拿吃的东西。 - 好。
Get something to eat. - OK.
哇, 捕捉那!
Whoa, catch that!
你看见那吗?
Did you see that?
仍旧敏捷。
Still got the moves.
是的!
Yeah!
你为什么停止?
Why are you stopping?
她正在这里做什么? Gary,你应该打电话给她的代理人。
What is she doing here? Gary, you were supposed to call her agent.
嗨，甜心。
Hi, honey.
我们试着联络你。
We tried to reach you.
对不起。
I'm sorry.
一位批评家? - 不，所有的纸,亲爱的。
One critic? - No, all the papers, dear.
玛丽珍・简。 坐下。 让我们解释它。 - 如果你喜欢,我们可以说你变成生病。
Mary Jane, honey. Sit down. Let's explain it to you. - If you like, we could say you became ill.
那如此贫乏地被处理。 - 是的。 仅仅给了我们预演。
That was so poorly handled. - Yeah. Let's just rehearse.
所有人的玛丽,蜘蛛!
All right, Spidey!
对不起,过错。 让我看见那个华丽的微笑。
Excuse me, miss. Let me see that gorgeous smile.
嗨， Eddie 。
Hi, Eddie.
你是如此美丽。
You're so beautiful.
这是第一版东西。
This is front page stuff.
我必须练习。 我将看见你比较迟,好?
I've got to practice. I'll see you later, OK?
如何大约今晚? - 不是今晚。
How about tonight? - Not tonight.
为什么不?
Why not?
觉得 我们有那令人惊异的-- 夜晚。
Think of that amazing-- night that we had.
我们有了咖啡， Eddie 。
We had a coffee, Eddie.
嗨,美丽的。
Hey, beautiful.
再来些。
One more.
事情都好吗? - 是的。 我很好。
Everything OK? - Yeah. I'm fine.
你不对～我感到仍然疯狂,不是吗 ?
You're not still mad at me, are you?
不,彼得。 我是以为你。。。
No, Peter. I'm proud of you.
嗨。 我将要从 swingin' 那里摄。
Hey. I'm gonna be swingin' it from over there.
因此你知道该哪里看。
So you know where to look.
给他们一场好的表演。
Give 'em a good show.
不  为检讨担忧。
Don't worry about that review.
我们将要 明天晚上有关它笑。
We're gonna be laughing about it tomorrow night.
诺言。 - 是的。
Promise. - Yeah.
那不是来自那所监狱 正在休息的家伙?
Isn't that that guy from that prison break?
好象是他。
He fits.
嗨!你! 站住!
Hey you! Halt!
包围背面!
Cover the back!
开火!
Fire!
纽约的城市人们,我今天这里
People of the city of New York, I am here today
因为我跌落 62个层
because I fell 62 storeys
而且某人捕捉了我。
and someone caught me.
从不要求 任何事作为回报 的某人。
Someone who never asks for anything in return.
某人是谁 甚至不需要知道他是谁 我们……
Someone who doesn't even want us to know who he is.
嗨， 玛丽珍 。 - 哈利。
Hey, MJ. - Harry.
彼得 在哪里?
Where is Pete?
拍一些动人的某人照片,我猜测。
Um-- taking somebody's picture, I guess.
我是如此快乐看见你的。 你看起来如此好。
I'm so happy to see you. You look so good.
我从未觉得更舒服。
I've never felt better.
它是怪异的感觉而不是博学的纽约。
It's a weird feeling, not knowing New York.
头上的撞击, 我仅仅是自由的如一只鸟。
Bump on the head, I'm just free as a bird.
你将会把我碰撞到头吗? - Bop。
Will you bump me on the head? - Bop.
嗨， 彼得 说你是在一场游戏中。
Hey, Pete said you're in a play.
你来。 你送我花。
You came. You sent me flowers.
我做?
I did?
我今晚再一次将来。
I'll come again tonight.
你不能。
You can't.
我-- 我是让去。
I--I was let go.
发生什麽事。
What happened.
我不很好。
I wasn't very good.
你知道,这正在困窘,但是...
You know, this is embarrassing, but...
我一次在中学中写你一场游戏。
I once wrote you a play in high school.
你写我一场游戏?
You wrote me a play?
是的。 - 哈利,那是最甜的事物。
Yeah. - Harry, that's the sweetest thing.
我问你: 当你正在没有一个降落伞降低的时候
I ask you: When you're dropping without a parachute
或你的正被抢夺的商店
or your store's being robbed
或你的房子是在燃烧,
or your house is on fire,
它是谁 brakes 你的秋天,放外面的火焰而且消失你的孩子?
who is it that brakes your fall, puts out the flames and saves your children?
蜘蛛-人!
Spider-Man!
他们爱我!
They love me!
然后让我们听到它! 对於你的一和唯一的友好附近...
Then let's hear it! For your one and only friendly neighborhood...
蜘蛛-人!
Spider-Man!
吻他! 吻他!
Kiss him! Kiss him!
前进吧, 这是它绑在我身上的权利。
Go ahead, lay it right on me.
真的吗? - 是的,他们将会爱它。
Really? - Yeah, they'll love it.
吻他! 吻他! - 不,蜘蛛-人,不!
Kiss him! Kiss him! - No, Spider-Man, no!
权利...
Right...
希望 彼得 拍得到这。
Hope Pete's getting a shot of this.
嗨,你还好吗? - 是的，我很好。
Hey, are you OK? - Yes, I'm fine.
捷格舞提高,朋友。
Jig's up, pal.
我不  想要伤害你。
I don't want to hurt you.
现在离开。 - 我猜测你没有听到?
Leave now. - I guess you haven't heard?
我是警长 '回合这些部份。
I'm the sheriff 'round these parts.
好。
OK.
所有的这些家伙来自哪里呢?
Where do all these guys come from?
Bonsoir。 Le monsieur 一-t- il un"保留"?（法文）
Bonsoir. Le monsieur a-t-il un "reservation"?
对不起,我不  说。。。 - 但是这是一家法国的餐厅,不是吗?
I'm sorry, I don't speak... - But this is a French restaurant, non?
Oui是。（法文）
Oui.
命名? - 彼得・帕克。
Name, please? - Parker, Peter.
啊。 我们这里。
Ah. Here we are.
桌子为二。 Pekar。（法文）
Table for two. Pekar.
帕克。 - 那是我说的算。
Parker. - That is what I said.
Pekar。（法文）
Pekar.
Um,我有一个请求。
Um, I have a request.
我的女朋友将会过来,
My girlfriend will be coming,
而且我有这个戒指。
and I have this ring.
啊。 所有的?
Ah. All?
哦,因此你今晚想要取出问题,hein?
Oh, so you want to pop the question tonight, hein?
是的，而且我想要做非常特别的东西。
Yes, and I want to do something very special.
我爱它。
I love it.
浪漫史。
Romance.
我是法国的。
I am French.
当我向你作信号的时候，是否你将会带着一些香槟酒。。。
When I signal you, if you'd bring some champagne with the ring...
在酒杯中放进一些……?
In ze bottom of her glass?
最好了。 - Magnifique。
Perfect. - Magnifique.
我也想, 同时
Also I thought, at the same time
可以音乐家
could the musicians
放这首歌?
play this song?
他们的喜欢事物。
Their favorite.